[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "blue",
        "back": "синий",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "yellow",
        "back": "жёлтый",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "green",
        "back": "зелёный",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "cyan",
        "back": "бирюзовый",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "magenta",
        "back": "маджента",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "white",
        "back": "белый",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "black",
        "back": "черный",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "gray",
        "back": "серый",
        "setId": "colours"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "Scattergun",
        "back": "Scout's stock shotgun",
        "setId": "tf2"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "Direct Hit",
        "back": "Soldier's rocket launcher. Deals no splash damage, but increased damage on direct hits",
        "setId": "tf2"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "Bazaar Bargain",
        "back": "Sniper's sniper rifle that increases it's charge up time based on the amoun of headshots that have been achieved this life",
        "setId": "tf2"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "Axetinguisher",
        "back": "Pyro's axe that Crits when hitting burning enemies and gives a speedboost upon killing them",
        "setId": "tf2"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "Crusader's Crossbow",
        "back": "Medic's crossbow. Heals when teammates are hit and deals damage when hit enemies",
        "setId": "tf2"
    }
]